http://www.ineos.com/information/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This website is owned and run by INEOS AG (“INEOS”, “us” or “we”) on behalf of the INEOS group of companies. This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you provide to us when you use this website.
INEOS is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
INEOS may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25th May 2018.
INEOS O&P Europe Documentation
Here you will find documentation detailing Data Protection information across the European businesses.
GDPR Info - INEOS Sales UK (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Sales Norway (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Sales Italia (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Sales Belgium - Spanish branch (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Sales Belgium (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Koeln (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS France SAS (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Europe (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Derivatives France (EN)
GDPR Info - INEOS Commercial Services (EN)
What we collect
We collect personal information from users of our website who submit graduate job applications forms via the website.
In addition, servers located within INEOS and hosted by third party service providers automatically log data about your visit to our site based on your IP address. This information does not identify you as an individual, but identifies the computer or other device you use to access the website. This information we collect is used to see where the site is being used in the world to ensure coverage, and for click stream analysis to help better understand site usage.
What we do with the information we gather
We collect personal information in job applications that are submitted on the website. We require this information as part of our recruitment process to consider the suitability of job applicants. In addition we may periodically send e-mails about other information which we think you may find interesting using the e-mail address which you have provided.
We also hold information for registration to certain parts of our site. This information is held to permit access to certain parts of the site. It is not used for marketing purposes.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
Please see our Cookie Policy for further details of how we use Cookies on this website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email richard.longden@ineos.com.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at richard.longden@ineos.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
How to contact us
Please e-mail us at richard.longden@ineos.com if you have any questions about our privacy policy or the information we hold about you.
We use cookies to make sure you get the most from our website. Need to know more?
OK
Company
INEOS is a global manufacturer of petrochemicals, speciality chemicals and oil products. It comprises 34 businesses each with a major chemical company heritage. Its production network spans 183 sites in 26 countries throughout the world.
Learn More
Overview
INEOS at a glance
Our Profile
Product Overview
Vision and Values
Leadership
SHE
